<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Careers on RedBlueDefence</title><link>https://redbluedefence.com/careers/</link><description>Recent content in Careers on RedBlueDefence</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://redbluedefence.com/careers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Security Architect</title><link>https://redbluedefence.com/careers/cloud-security-architect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redbluedefence.com/careers/cloud-security-architect/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="role-overview"&gt;Role Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Cloud Security Architect, you will be responsible for designing and implementing comprehensive security architectures for cloud-based systems and applications. This role requires deep expertise in cloud platforms, security frameworks, and the ability to balance security requirements with business objectives and operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will work with cross-functional teams to ensure security is built into cloud solutions from the ground up, not bolted on as an afterthought. This position offers the opportunity to shape the future of cloud security in a rapidly growing organization.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Penetration Tester</title><link>https://redbluedefence.com/careers/penetration-tester/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://redbluedefence.com/careers/penetration-tester/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="role-overview"&gt;Role Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Penetration Tester, you will be responsible for conducting authorized simulated attacks on our clients&amp;rsquo; systems to identify vulnerabilities before malicious actors can exploit them. This role combines technical expertise with creative problem-solving to help organizations strengthen their security posture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="key-responsibilities"&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conduct comprehensive penetration testing on web applications, networks, mobile applications, and cloud infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perform vulnerability assessments and security audits to identify weaknesses in client systems and applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>